(window.webpackJsonp=window.webpackJsonp||[]).push([[0],{24:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n.p+"static/media/logo.ee9e8b1b.svg"},27:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n(51)},32:function(e,t,n){},46:function(e,t,n){},51:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var o=n(0),r=n.n(o),i=n(15),c=n.n(i),a=n(12),s=(n(32),n(4)),l=n(23),u=n(6),p=n(7),y=n(10),m=n(9),h=n(11),d=n(8),f=n(14),w=[{question:"What decade did formal research in AI begin ?",answers:[{type:"incorrect-1",content:"1940s"},{type:"incorrect-2",content:"1960s"},{type:"correct",content:"1980s"},{type:"incorrect",content:"2000s "}]},{question:"The area of AI that investigates on methods of facilitating communication between people and computer is :",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Machine learning"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Symbolic processing"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Decision Support"},{type:"correct",content:"Natural language processing"}]},{question:"The practice of using algorithms to parse data, learn from it, and then make a determination or prediction about something is :",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"Machine learning"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Symbolic processing"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Decision Support"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Natural language processing"}]},{question:"A language model is composed in  a set of elements, which does not include:",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Language units"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Role structure of units"},{type:"incorrect",content:"System constraints"},{type:"correct",content:"Structural units"}]},{question:"Which of the following methods is NOT a learning method ?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Memorization"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Analogy"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Deduction"},{type:"correct",content:"Introduction"}]},{question:"Which programming language is NOT commonly used for AI?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"PROLOG"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Python"},{type:"incorrect",content:"LISP"},{type:"correct",content:"Perl"}]},{question:"Which of the following concepts is a component of an expert system?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Inference engine"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Knowledge base"},{type:"incorrect",content:"User interface"},{type:"correct",content:"All of the above"}]},{question:"Who is considered as the \u201cfather\u201d of artificial intelligence?",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"Fisher Ada"},{type:"incorrect",content:"John McCarthy"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Allen Newell"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Alan Turing"}]},{question:"What is the goal of artificial intelligence?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"To solve real-world problems"},{type:"incorrect",content:"To solve artificial problems"},{type:"correct",content:"To explain various sorts of intelligence"},{type:"incorrect",content:"To extract scientific causes"}]},{question:"How does a decision tree make a decision ?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"After a single test"},{type:"incorrect",content:"After two tests"},{type:"correct",content:"After a sequence of tests"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Without a test"}]},{question:"What takes an object described by a set of attributes as input?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Random forest"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Decision graph"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Decision tree"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"What are the tasks an AI system can perform?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Act as a virtual assistant"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Automate manual processes"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Analyze unstructured data"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"Which of the following is an application of natural language processing?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Voice assistants like Amazon Alexa and Siri"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Chatbots"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Sentiment analysis"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"While evaluating a classifier\u2019s performance, what do we mean by the \u2018sensitivity\u2019 of our model?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"False positive rate"},{type:"correct",content:"True positive rate"},{type:"incorrect",content:"False negative rate"},{type:"incorrect",content:"True negative rate"}]},{question:"What is the Bayes theorem formula?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"\tP(A\u2502B)=(P(B) P(B|A)) / (P(A))"},{type:"incorrect",content:"\tP(A\u2502B)=(P(A) P(B|A)) / (P(A))"},{type:"correct",content:"\tP(A\u2502B)=(P(A) P(B|A)) / ( P(B))"},{type:"incorrect",content:"\tP(A\u2502B)=(P(B) P(B|A)) / (P(B))"}]},{question:"Which of the following is true about model capacity (the ability of a neural network to approximate complex functions)?",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"As number of hidden layers increase, model capacity increases"},{type:"incorrect",content:"As dropout ratio increases, model capacity increases"},{type:"incorrect",content:"As learning rate increases, model capacity increases"},{type:"incorrect",content:"None of these"}]},{question:"What is(are) an(some) advantage(s) of decision trees?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Possible Scenarios can be added"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Interpretability of the model"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Worst, best and expected values can be determined for different scenarios"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"In unsupervised learning :",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Specific output values are given"},{type:"correct",content:"Output values are not given"},{type:"incorrect",content:"No specific inputs are given"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Both inputs and outputs are given"}]},{question:"Neural Networks are complex ______________with many parameters",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Linear Functions "},{type:"correct",content:"Nonlinear Functions"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Discrete Functions"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Exponential Functions"}]},{question:"What is a perceptron?",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"a single layer feed-forward neural network with pre-processing"},{type:"incorrect",content:"an auto-associative neural network"},{type:"incorrect",content:"a double layer auto-associative neural network "},{type:"incorrect",content:"a neural network that contains feedback"}]},{question:"In which of the following learning paradigm the agent receives rewards and punishements based on the outcome?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Active Learning"},{type:"correct",content:"Reinforcement Learning "},{type:"incorrect",content:"Supervised learning "},{type:"incorrect",content:"Unsupervised learning"}]},{question:"Decision trees are appropriate for the problems where : ",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"The output is numerical"},{type:"incorrect",content:"The output is nominal categorical"},{type:"incorrect",content:"The output is ordinal categorical "},{type:"correct",content:"All of the mentioned "}]},{question:"How can back propagation be defined ? ",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Another name given to the curvy function "},{type:"incorrect",content:"The transmission of error back through the network to adjust the inputs "},{type:"correct",content:"The transmission of error back through the network to ajdust weights "},{type:"incorrect",content:"None of these"}]},{question:"In Bayes theorem, what is meant by P(Hi|E)?",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"The probability that hypotheses Hi is true given evidence E"},{type:"incorrect",content:"The probability that hypotheses Hi is false given evidence E"},{type:"incorrect",content:"The probability that hypotheses Hi is true given false evidence E"},{type:"incorrect",content:"The probability that hypotheses Hi is false given false evidence E"}]},{question:"What text mining technique can be used for noise reduction?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Lemmatization"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Word embeddings"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Stemming"},{type:"correct",content:"A and C"}]},{question:"What is the most efficient way of handling missing or corrupted categorical data in terms of information loss reduction?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Drop missing rows or columns"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Replace missing values with mean, median, and mode"},{type:"correct",content:"Assign a unique category to missing values"},{type:"incorrect",content:"All of the mentioned"}]},{question:"Which of the following is enabled by the kernel trick?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Regularization"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Non-linear flexibility"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Variance of the estimator reduction"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"What technique(s) could be used to adjust the parameters and minimize the cost function?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Exhaustive Search"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Random Search"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Bayesian Optimization"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"What could be the reason for the loss to not decrease in the first few epochs while training a neural network?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"The learning rate is low"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Regularization parameter is high"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Stuck at local minima"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"What regularization process(es) enable(s) deep neural architectures training?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Batch normalization"},{type:"incorrect",content:"ELU activation functions"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Fully convolutionnal layers "},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"Computational learning theory analyzes the sample complexity and computational complexity of :",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Unsupervised Learning"},{type:"correct",content:"Inductive learning"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Forced based learning"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Weak learning"}]},{question:"The RBF kernel on two samples x and x', represented as feature vectors in some input space, is defined as: ",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"\ud835\udc3e (\ud835\udc65,\ud835\udc65\u2032)=exp(\u2212||\ud835\udc65\u2212\ud835\udc65\u2032||22\ud835\udf0e2) "},{type:"incorrect",content:"\ud835\udc3e (\ud835\udc65,\ud835\udc65\u2032)=\u2212exp(\u2212||\ud835\udc65\u2212\ud835\udc65\u2032||22\ud835\udf0e2) "},{type:"incorrect",content:"\ud835\udc3e (\ud835\udc65,\ud835\udc65\u2032)=exp(\u2212||\ud835\udc65+\ud835\udc65\u2032||22\ud835\udf0e2) "},{type:"incorrect",content:"\ud835\udc3e (\ud835\udc65,\ud835\udc65\u2032)=exp(\u2212||\u2212(\ud835\udc65\u2212\ud835\udc65\u2032)||22\ud835\udf0e2) "}]},{question:"If a decision process outputs positive evidence to reject an hypothesis, but in reality the hypothesis holds, it is a: ",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Type II error"},{type:"incorrect",content:"False negative"},{type:"correct",content:"Type I error"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Specialized hypothesis"}]},{question:"Which of the following is also called exploratory learning?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Supervised learning"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Active learning "},{type:"correct",content:"Unsupervised learning "},{type:"incorrect",content:"Reinforcement learning "}]},{question:"In language processing, which levels of knowledge are not included?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Semantical"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Syntactical"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Pragmatical"},{type:"correct",content:"All of mentioned"}]},{question:"WHow is the process of deleting certain neurons at random during the training of a neural network called?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Random subsampling"},{type:"correct",content:"Dropout"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Batch normalization"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Neural killing"}]},{question:"What name(s) can be given to some decision tree nodes?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Decision Nodes"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Leaves"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Chance Nodes"},{type:"correct",content:"All of the mentioned"}]},{question:"What is the maximum likelihood estimator of beta in Y Xbeta + epsilon for the training set {(xi,yi)}i ",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"beta = (XTX)-1XTy"},{type:"incorrect",content:"beta = (XXT)-1XTy"},{type:"incorrect",content:"beta = (XTX)-1Xy "},{type:"incorrect",content:"beta = (XXT)-1Xy"}]},{question:"What is the maximum likelihood estimator for the ridge regression ? ",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"beta = (XTX+lambdaI)-1XTy"},{type:"incorrect",content:"beta = (XXT+lambdaI)-1XTy "},{type:"incorrect",content:"beta = (XTX+lambdaI)-1Xy"},{type:"incorrect",content:"beta = (XXT+lambdaI)-1Xy"}]},{question:"What is an auto-associative network?",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"A neural network containing no loop"},{type:"correct",content:"A neural network that contains a feedback"},{type:"incorrect",content:"A neural network with only one loop "},{type:"incorrect",content:"A single layer feed-forward neural network with pre-processing"}]},{question:"Among the following, which one is not a horn clause? ",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"p"},{type:"incorrect",content:"\xd8p V q "},{type:"incorrect",content:"p \u2192 q"},{type:"correct",content:"p \u2192 \xd8q"}]},{question:"Among the following, which one is not a horn clause? ",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"p"},{type:"incorrect",content:"\xd8p V q "},{type:"incorrect",content:"p \u2192 q"},{type:"correct",content:"p \u2192 \xd8q"}]},{question:"What is the relationship between a node and its predecessors in a bayesian network ",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"Functionnally dependent"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Dependant "},{type:"correct",content:"Conditionally independent"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Both Conditionally dependent and Dependant"}]},{question:"Which type of penalty can be, in some cases, interpreted as performing features selection (shrinking some weights exactly to zero)",answers:[{type:"incorrect",content:"L2 penalty"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Dropout"},{type:"correct",content:"L1 penalty"},{type:"incorrect",content:"Elastic net"}]},{question:"What is the LASSO optimization problem?",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"min\ud835\udefd0,\ud835\udefd{1\ud835\udc41 \u2211(\ud835\udc66\ud835\udc56\u2212\ud835\udefd0\u2212 \ud835\udc65\ud835\udc56\ud835\udc47\ud835\udefd)2\ud835\udc41\ud835\udc56=1} \ud835\udc60\ud835\udc62\ud835\udc4f\ud835\udc57\ud835\udc52\ud835\udc50\ud835\udc61 \ud835\udc61\ud835\udc5c \u2211|\ud835\udefd\ud835\udc57|\ud835\udc5d\ud835\udc57=1\u2264\ud835\udc61 "},{type:"incorrect",content:"min\ud835\udefd0,\ud835\udefd{1\ud835\udc41 \u2211(\ud835\udc66\ud835\udc56\u2212\ud835\udefd0\u2212 \ud835\udc65\ud835\udc56\ud835\udc47\ud835\udefd)2\ud835\udc41\ud835\udc56=1} \ud835\udc60\ud835\udc62\ud835\udc4f\ud835\udc57\ud835\udc52\ud835\udc50\ud835\udc61 \ud835\udc61\ud835\udc5c \u2211\ud835\udefd\ud835\udc572\ud835\udc5d\ud835\udc57=1\u2264\ud835\udc61 "},{type:"incorrect",content:"min\ud835\udefd0,\ud835\udefd{1\ud835\udc41 \u2211(\ud835\udc66\ud835\udc56\u2212\ud835\udefd0\u2212 \ud835\udc65\ud835\udc56\ud835\udc47\ud835\udefd)2\ud835\udc41\ud835\udc56=1} \ud835\udc60\ud835\udc62\ud835\udc4f\ud835\udc57\ud835\udc52\ud835\udc50\ud835\udc61 \ud835\udc61\ud835\udc5c \u2211|\ud835\udefd\ud835\udc57|2\ud835\udc5d\ud835\udc57=1\u2264\ud835\udc61 "},{type:"incorrect",content:"min\ud835\udefd0,\ud835\udefd{1\ud835\udc41 \u2211(\ud835\udc66\ud835\udc56\u2212\ud835\udefd0\u2212 \ud835\udc65\ud835\udc56\ud835\udc47\ud835\udefd)2\ud835\udc41\ud835\udc56=1} \ud835\udc60\ud835\udc62\ud835\udc4f\ud835\udc57\ud835\udc52\ud835\udc50\ud835\udc61 \ud835\udc61\ud835\udc5c \u2211\ud835\udefd\ud835\udc572\ud835\udc5d\ud835\udc57=1\u2264\u2212\ud835\udc61 "}]},{question:"Why is Weight Initialization important in Neural Networks? ",answers:[{type:"correct",content:"To prevent gradient from vanishing during the course of a backward pass "},{type:"incorrect",content:"To increase the accuracy of the model"},{type:"incorrect",content:"To use memory more efficiently "},{type:"incorrect",content:"For regularization purposes "}]}];w.forEach(function(e,t){return e.answers.forEach(function(e,n){"incorrect"===e.type&&(e.type="incorrect-".concat(t,"-").concat(n))})});var g=w,v=n(5);var b=function(e){return r.a.createElement("h2",{className:"question"},e.content)};var q=function(e){return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"questionCount"},"Question ",r.a.createElement("span",null,e.counter)," of ",r.a.createElement("span",null,e.total))};var A=function(e){return r.a.createElement("li",{className:"answerOption"},r.a.createElement("input",{type:"radio",className:"radioCustomButton",name:"radioGroup",checked:e.answerType===e.answer,id:e.answerType,value:e.answerType,disabled:e.answer,onChange:e.onAnswerSelected}),r.a.createElement("label",{className:"radioCustomLabel",htmlFor:e.answerType},e.answerContent))};var E=function(e){return r.a.createElement(v.CSSTransitionGroup,{className:"container",component:"div",transitionName:"fade",transitionEnterTimeout:800,transitionLeaveTimeout:500,transitionAppear:!0,transitionAppearTimeout:500},r.a.createElement("div",{key:e.questionId},r.a.createElement(q,{counter:e.questionId,total:e.questionTotal}),r.a.createElement(b,{content:e.question}),r.a.createElement("ul",{className:"answerOptions"},e.answerOptions.map(function(t,n){return r.a.createElement(A,{key:t.content,index:n,answerContent:t.content,answerType:t.type,answer:e.answer,questionId:e.questionId,onAnswerSelected:e.onAnswerSelected})}))))},T=function(e){var t=e.formErrors;return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"formErrors"},Object.keys(t).map(function(e,n){return t[e].length>0?r.a.createElement("p",{key:n},e," ",t[e]):""}))},k=function(e){function t(e){var n;return Object(u.a)(this,t),(n=Object(y.a)(this,Object(m.a)(t).call(this,e))).handleUserInput=function(e){var t=e.target.name,o=e.target.value;n.setState(Object(s.a)({},t,o),function(){n.validateField(t,o)})},n.storeWinnerEmail=function(){var e=n.state.email,t=JSON.parse(localStorage.getItem("emails"));t.push(e),localStorage.setItem("emails",JSON.stringify(t))},n.state={email:"",formErrors:{email:""},emailValid:!1,formValid:!1},n}return Object(h.a)(t,e),Object(p.a)(t,[{key:"validateField",value:function(e,t){var n=this.state.formErrors,o=this.state.emailValid;switch(e){case"email":o=t.match(/^([\w.%+-]+)@([\w-]+\.)+([\w]{2,})$/i),n.email=o?"":" is invalid"}this.setState({formErrors:n,emailValid:o},this.validateForm)}},{key:"validateForm",value:function(){this.setState({formValid:this.state.emailValid})}},{key:"errorClass",value:function(e){return 0===e.length?"":"has-error"}},{key:"render",value:function(){return r.a.createElement("form",{className:"demoForm"},r.a.createElement("h2",null,"Congratulations, you have won the quizz !"),r.a.createElement("h3",null,"Type your email in order to partifcipate to the draw and win an iPad "),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"form-group ".concat(this.errorClass(this.state.formErrors.email))},r.a.createElement("label",{htmlFor:"email"},"Email address"),r.a.createElement("input",{type:"email",required:!0,className:"form-control",name:"email",placeholder:"Email",value:this.state.email,onChange:this.handleUserInput})),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"panel panel-default"},r.a.createElement(T,{formErrors:this.state.formErrors})),r.a.createElement("button",{type:"submit",className:"btn btn-primary",disabled:!this.state.formValid,onClick:this.storeWinnerEmail},"Submit"))}}]),t}(o.Component),S=function(){return window.location.reload()};var N=function(e){var t;return"lost"===e.quizResult&&(t=r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement("p",null,"You failed the quizz..."),r.a.createElement("button",{onClick:S}," Try again ?"))),"win"===e.quizResult&&(t=r.a.createElement(k,null)),r.a.createElement(v.CSSTransitionGroup,{className:"container result",component:"div",transitionName:"fade",transitionEnterTimeout:800,transitionLeaveTimeout:500,transitionAppear:!0,transitionAppearTimeout:500},t)},O=n(24),W=n.n(O),I=(n(46),function(e){function t(e){var n;return Object(u.a)(this,t),(n=Object(y.a)(this,Object(m.a)(t).call(this,e))).state={counter:0,questionId:1,question:"",answerOptions:[],answer:"",answersCount:{},result:"",questionsCount:10,quizzTitle:"Qim Quizz"},n.handleAnswerSelected=n.handleAnswerSelected.bind(Object(d.a)(Object(d.a)(n))),n}return Object(h.a)(t,e),Object(p.a)(t,[{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){var e=this,t=this.shuffleArray(g),n=t.map(function(t){return e.shuffleArray(t.answers)});this.setState({question:t[0].question,answerOptions:n[0]})}},{key:"shuffleArray",value:function(e){for(var t,n,o=e.length;0!==o;)n=Math.floor(Math.random()*o),t=e[o-=1],e[o]=e[n],e[n]=t;return e}},{key:"handleAnswerSelected",value:function(e){var t=this;this.setUserAnswer(e.currentTarget.value),this.state.questionId<this.state.questionsCount?setTimeout(function(){return t.setNextQuestion()},300):setTimeout(function(){return t.setResults(t.getResults())},300)}},{key:"setUserAnswer",value:function(e){this.setState(function(t,n){return{answersCount:Object(l.a)({},t.answersCount,Object(s.a)({},e,(t.answersCount[e]||0)+1)),answer:e}})}},{key:"setNextQuestion",value:function(){var e=this.state.counter+1,t=this.state.questionId+1;this.setState({counter:e,questionId:t,question:g[e].question,answerOptions:g[e].answers,answer:""})}},{key:"getResults",value:function(){return this.state.answersCount.correct===this.state.questionsCount?"win":"lost"}},{key:"setResults",value:function(e){this.setState({result:e})}},{key:"renderQuiz",value:function(){return r.a.createElement(E,{answer:this.state.answer,answerOptions:this.state.answerOptions,questionId:this.state.questionId,question:this.state.question,questionTotal:this.state.questionsCount,onAnswerSelected:this.handleAnswerSelected})}},{key:"renderResult",value:function(){return r.a.createElement(N,Object.assign({},this.state,{quizResult:this.state.result}))}},{key:"render",value:function(){return r.a.createElement(a.a,null,r.a.createElement("div",{className:"App"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"App-header"},r.a.createElement("img",{src:W.a,className:"App-logo",alt:"logo"}),r.a.createElement("h2",{style:{color:"#CFDE00"}}," ",this.state.quizzTitle)),this.state.result?this.renderResult():this.renderQuiz()),r.a.createElement(f.c,null,r.a.createElement(f.a,{path:"/winners",component:z})))}}]),t}(o.Component));function C(e){return r.a.createElement("p",null,e)}var z=function(e){function t(){return Object(u.a)(this,t),Object(y.a)(this,Object(m.a)(t).apply(this,arguments))}return Object(h.a)(t,e),Object(p.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e=JSON.parse(localStorage.getItem("emails"));return r.a.createElement(v.CSSTransitionGroup,{className:"container result",component:"div",transitionName:"fade",transitionEnterTimeout:800,transitionLeaveTimeout:500,transitionAppear:!0,transitionAppearTimeout:500},r.a.createElement("h2",null,"Winners"),e.map(C))}}]),t}(o.Component),x=I;Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));c.a.render(r.a.createElement(a.a,null,r.a.createElement(x,null)),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then(function(e){e.unregister()})}},[[27,2,1]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.58a7dafc.chunk.js.map